[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 5, "question": "What will it take to stop the bloodshed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 6, "answer": "This is our best chance in more than a decade to take commonsense steps that will save lives.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "Well, we certainly wouldn't want somebody like that shooter to have that much arsenal at his disposal, and we must make changes so that we do find out these people in advance and stop that before massacres occur.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "What can America do to try and identify them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "And that's a great point.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "JJR", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "At what point do the lawmakers of America say we're going to try and stop the increase in the sale of assault weapons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Our governor put it very well when he said what more do we need to know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "I mean, if the only thing that comes out of all this, out of the senseless massacre of 20 young children at Sandy Hook, is background checks, doesn't that qualify for a shameful response, the type that President Obama is talking about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "DT", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "I would be very, very disappointed and I think many of the -- many of the families would be disappointed if that was the only thing that came out of all -- all of this tragedy, the background checks.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sandy Hook", "Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "What are these likely to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "Well, an NRA certificate just means, I'll assume, that they either attended a class or obtained the material that's available in libraries all across the country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "What is the problem, really, ideologically even for the NRA, which had a lot of members obviously who like guns, what is the problem in just reducing the freedom of people like Adam Lanza to buy assault rifles like an AR-15?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "WP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "Well, the problem is that we're using terminology very loosely and we have to be very careful when we use terminology that we're even talking about the same thing at the same time.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"], "PERSON": ["Adam Lanza"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "How can that be logical to an intelligent adult mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "You know, if you double the number of guns owned by people who aren't misusing them, it's going to have no impact.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Well, I just think people are just flabbergasted to hear this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Dana Loesch, how can that be an appropriate response to what happened at Sandy Hook?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Well, simply, Piers, because we have gun laws already on the books.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dana Loesch"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["L.A.", "Connecticut"], "PERSON": ["Adam Lanza"]}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "At what point, Dana, do you say, you know what, we're just going to make it tougher for people to be able to have this kind of arsenal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Well, Piers, you realize that Adam Lanza, according to the \"L.A. Times,\" the \"Portland Observer,\" numerous local media report in Connecticut, he did try to purchase a firearm.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Why is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Well, I think if you look at the history of gun laws, make a list of which cities and states have the most oppressive gun laws.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States", "Brazil", "South Africa", "Australia", "Britain"]}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "CC", "RB", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "How do you explain that, Grover, in any rational way that convinces me that countries that don't have guns in mass circulation have almost no gun crime?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Well, if you compare apples and apples and look at the United States, and obviously Brazil and South Africa and other countries have a great number of gun crimes and they have very serious gun laws, so gun laws haven't solved the problem in other countries, and where you put in more gun laws in Australia and Britain you've had more crime in general.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Grover"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Van?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Well, first of all, that's just actually not true but I want to say a couple of things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "That's not -- it's a false premise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 305, "question": "Do you know more about these weapons than General McChrystal does?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Evidently because --", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["General McChrystal"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Are you telling me that doesn't qualify as an assault weapon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "By the technical definition, no, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "-- to the shooting dead 26 people in five minutes?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "Hold on, hold on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "-- that has nothing to do -- I'm sorry, you said?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "By the way, the latest CBS poll shows that support for these gun control measures is tanking.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dana"]}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CD", "VBZ", "RBR", "IN", "CD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Seven lives lost are OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "VBD", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "You know what, Dana, seven is better than 30, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Dana, when did I say disarmament?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "I'm taking it down -- I'm using your logic and going down that road.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Is the gay marriage debate lost to those that oppose it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Well, it's an interesting question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Dana Loesch, what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "I'm not quite sure whether or not it's lost.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dana Loesch"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Is it that kind of repositioning?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "It's sad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["KKK"]}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "NNP", "DT", "IN", ",", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNPS", ":", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNPS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Isn't that an incredibly salient point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "You know what, Republicans all throughout, Piers -- I agree with that because Republicans -- that's why you have the Republican party because they split from Democrats and they split from -- you know, the KKK was the militant faction of that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Can I respond to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Unfortunately, Van, we've got to move on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "What do you make of that, Grover Norquist?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "Well, she's had a tremendous career.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Grover Norquist"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barbara Walters"]}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Dana Loesch, can we reach any point of agreement on Barbara Walters?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "I grew up watching Barbara Walters.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dana Loesch", "Barbara Walters"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Van?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "I have had the honor to be on \"The View\" with her, watching her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "Isn't that quite extraordinary?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "It is, but you know my father is a very humble man, and if you were to ask him about that, you know, he would just kind of say, aw, shucks and want to talk about something else.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "But do they know each other?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "I don't think they ever met.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Do you think there's some merit to that argument?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "I'm sure there's some merit to the argument.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "Aren't we in the same position here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "I don't think so, no, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "What message would he have to people on Easter, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "That Jesus Christ has risen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]